Republic of Belarus, Minsk city, Dzerzhinsky street 19

> Phone number +375 25 541 38 74

> > **Email**

Address

dianalyah23@gmail.com

FRONT-END **DEVELOPER**

Attentive to the details web developer with 3+ years of front end experience and passion for responsive website design and mobile application development. My skills, knowledge and an analytical mindset, will be used to create a user-friendly app or website. Ready for relocate.



EXPERIENCES

REACT NATIVE DEVELOPER Severex OCTOBER 2022 - PRESENT

DEVELOPMENT OF MOBILE APPLICATIONS ON REACT NATIVE(IOS, ANDROID):

- CREATION AND SUPPORT OF THE FRONT-END PART OF APPLICATIONS;
- CREATION OF LOGIC FOR RECEIVING AND SENDING DATA TO THE SERVER;
- DEVELOPMENT OF USER INTERFACE FOR APPLICATIONS;
- IMPLEMENTATION OF NAVIGATION;
- WORK WITH ANIMATION;
- CONNECTION OF ANALYTICS;
- ASSEMBLING APPLICATION BUILDS AND UPLOADING THEM TO GOOGLE PLAY AND APPLE STORE;
- WORK WITH FIREBASE, SWAGGE, FIGMA;
- WORK WITH BUGS.

JAVASCRIPT DEVELOPER FREELANCE (SELF EMPLOYED) Freelance **JANUARY 2021 - SEPTEMBER 2021**

DEVELOPING REACT APPS:

- **USE CLASS COMPONENTS**
- USE COMPONENT OF MATERIAL UI;
- LAYOUT USING CSS;
- REDUX CONNECTION;
- WORK WITH GITHIB.

WORKING ON MY OWN PROJECTS:

- CANDY SHOP
- CONNECTION OF FREE SERVICE (JSON) PLACEHOLDER.
- TO-DO LIST,
- SOCIAL NETWORK.

REACT AND REACT NATIVE DEVELOPER **Tapston Development** SEPTEMBER 2021 - PRESENT

DEVELOPMENT OF THE WEB ADMIN PART ON REACT:

- CREATION AND SUPPORT OF THE FRONT-END PART OF APPLICATIONS;
 - CREATION OF LOGIC FOR RECEIVING AND SENDING DATA TO THE SERVER;
- NAVIGATION;
- LAYOUT USING SCSS;
- CONNECTION OF LIBRARIES;
- WORK WITH BUGS;
- WORKING WITH THE DATABASE;
- CREATE REUSABLE COMPONENTS.

DEVELOPMENT OF MOBILE APPLICATIONS ON REACT NATIVE(IOS, ANDROID) AND INTERFACES FOR MANAGING THEIR CONTENT:

- CREATION AND SUPPORT OF THE FRONT-END PART OF APPLICATIONS;
- CREATION OF LOGIC FOR RECEIVING AND SENDING DATA TO THE SERVER;
- DEVELOPMENT OF USER INTERFACE FOR APPLICATIONS; IMPLEMENTATION OF NAVIGATION;
- WORK WITH ANIMATION;
- CONNECTION OF CARDS;
- CONNECTION OF ANALYTICS AND CRASHLITIKS;
- ASSEMBLING APPLICATION BUILDS AND UPLOADING THEM TO GOOGLE PLAY AND APPLE STORE;
- WORK WITH FIREBASE, SWAGGE, FIGMA;
- WORK WITH BUGS.

SKILLS

- **JAVASCRIPT**
- REACT NATIVE
- **REACT**
- HTML
- CSS
- SASS
- **REDUX TOOLKIT**
- REDUX
- **HOOKS**
- GIT
- **FLUX**
- UNIT TESTING
- **FIGMA**
- **FIREBASE**
- **SWAGGER**
- **TYPESCRIPT**

EDUCATION

Programming courses at IT-

INCUBATOR

2022

Belarusian State University of

Informatics and Radioelectronics,

Minsk

Belarusian State Technological

University,

Certification Specialist

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH - B2 (IN PROGRESS) RUSSIAN - NATIVE